Oğulcan Ünveren

Backend Developer

+905537290265 unverenogulcan@gmail.com Ankara/Türkiye



https://github.com/OgulcanUnveren

Summary

I am a web developer an bugbounty hunter having expertise in cyber security. I design and develop web applications using the latest technologies to deliver the product with quality code and make them secure to block security related threats.

Objective

Languages

Python

HTML

Eager to expand my skill set through making them habits,maybe obsessions. I never quit until I do my

Experience

NeuSEC

Difose

Backend Developer

Feb 2017 - Sep 2017

Worked for company's online existence and took role at building and making company's projects. Worked with Laravel and generally PHP and Python

Technologies

Algorithms

PHP

CSS

Progressive Web Apps

Javascript

English

SQL

Data Structures

WebRTC

C/C++

Backend Developer

Sarp Ozan Technology

Worked as system architect for integration of Openedx and custom django platforms. Worked with dockerized systems as full stack developer.

Restful API

Backend Developer

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Sep 2020 - Jan 2022

Created architecture for a Forensic Education Platform, company's websites security and System Administration. Experienced Forensic Techniques, Low Level Oday attacks and more. Worked with Python and PHP.

Frameworks

Metasploit

NodeJS Django

Laravel

Independent Pentester - Developer

Jun 2022 - present

Tools

Git

Bitbucket

Certificates

Advanced Entrepreneurship

Jul 2021 KOSGEB

Awarded for exceptional improvements made to improve user experience

Education

BSc - Economics

GAzi University

Sep 2015 - Jun 2021

OSCP Summer Camp

Bogazici University

Nov 2017

AAS - Web Desing and Coding

Anadolu University

Sep 2019 - May 2021